flysafair.co.za 2016-06-08

# 

**1.**

| 

**General**  
  
1.1. 

| 

“We” are Safair Operations (Proprietary) Limited and our address of establishment is at Northern Perimeter Road, O.R. Tambo International Airport, Bonaero Park, 1619, South Africa. We are a company incorporated in accordance with the laws of the Republic of South Africa and our Company registration number is 2007/032915/07.  
  
1.2.

| 

We are responsible for the processing of any personal information you provide to us via this Website or through other interactions with us.  
  
1.3.

| 

We take our responsibilities regarding protection of personal information very seriously. This policy explains how we use personal information we may obtain from you and about you. By using this Website you consent to this policy. By submitting your personal information you consent to the use of that personal information as set out in this privacy policy. If our privacy policy changes, we will post the changes on our Website. Continued use of our Website by you will signify that you agree to such changes.  
  
1.4.

| 

This policy is deemed to be an integral part of our website terms and conditions.  
  
**2.**

| 

**Why we need your personal information**  
  
2.1. 

| 

When you use services provided on this Website, you will be asked to provide certain information such as your name and contact details. We will store this information and use this information in the following ways:  
  
| 

(i) 

| 

to fulfil our agreement with you, including processing your flight, sending you your itinerary, or contacting you if there is a problem with your reservation;   
  
| 

(ii)

| 

to register you on our Website and administer our Website related services, such as our newsletter, where you have registered to receive these;   
  
| 

(iii)

| 

to administer any contest or other promotional offer you may enter and notify winners;   
  
| 

(iv)

| 

to administer our frequent flyer policy when it is implemented;   
  
| 

(v) 

| 

for crime prevention and detection;   
  
| 

(vi)

| 

to answer any queries which you may send us by e-mail or via our Website; and   
  
| 

(vii)

| 

for any other purpose regarding which we give information to you on this Websites.  
  
2.2.

| 

We need to know the names of all passengers travelling. If you are booking a flight on behalf of someone else, you must obtain their consent to use their personal information. You warrant that you have obtained this consent. If you have not obtained their consent, we ask that you do not provide us with their information until such time as you have obtained their consent.   
  
**3.**

| 

**Collection of information from you**  
  
3.1.

| 

The information which we collect may include the following:  
  
| 

(i)

| 

information collected from “cookies” as more fully explained in paragraph 3.2 below;  
  
| 

(ii)

| 

information collected when you register on our Website or fill out a form or make a booking; and/or  
  
| 

(iii) 

| 

any other information submitted to us via our Website or through your interactions with us.  
  
3.2.

| 

Use of “Cookies”  
  
| 

(i) 

| 

The Website makes use of "cookies".  
  
| 

(ii)

| 

A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on your internet browser on your computer. Cookies are used to provide information about your preferences on the Website so that we can provide you with better, more customised content and service in the future when you return to our Website.  
  
| 

(iii) 

| 

The only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you supply and it cannot read information off of your hard drive.  
  
**4.**

| 

**You can set their browser to alert yourself when you going to be sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it.**  
  
**5.**

| 

**How we use your personal information**  
  
5.1.

| 

Information that you provide or that is obtained by us will be used by us to enable us to review, develop and improve the services that we offer, and provide you and other customers (via newsletter, mail, e-mail telephone or otherwise) with information about new products and services and special offers we think you will find valuable. We may also inform you about new products and services and special offers of selected third parties. If you do not wish to have your details used in this way, please select the relevant tick box on the relevant page.  
  
5.2.

| 

We may provide this information to other companies who we believe have goods or services relevant to you which they would be able to offer to you. If you wish to have your details passed to such companies, please select the relevant tick box on the relevant page.  
  
5.3.

| 

We may also use your information for market research and statistical purposes in order to carry out appropriate research and analysis to monitor and improve use of our services. We may contact you (by post, e-mail, telephone or otherwise) to request your feedback and comments on our services.  
  
**6.**

| 

**How we protect your personal information**  
  
6.1.

| 

We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online. You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing over the internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default.  
  
**7.**

| 

**Access to information**  
  
7.1.

| 

You have the right to access your personal information.  
  
7.2.

| 

Should you require access to information or records, please refer to our [PAIA Manual](http://www.safair.co.za/uploads/news/Safair_PAIA_Manual_16_09_2013.pdf).
